

Adaeze Ndupu

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

A front-end developer with experience in development, and maintenance of websites and web applications. Proficiency in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, basic knowledge of React. Passionate about creating user-friendly websites and web applications that are easy to use by sticking to details and attaining pixel perfection.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address

Lagos, Nigeria

CONTACT

- andupu4@gmail.com
- +2348132284088
- o vermilion-resume.netlify.app
- Adaeze Ndupu
- vermilion4

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer Intern (chess plugin team)

ZURICHAT 2021 - 2022

Worked with a team to develop the front-end for the chess plugin in a new application called Zurichat.

Implemented the application's UI using HTML, CSS, and React.

Ensured that the UI was compatible with multiple browsers and responsive across multiple screen sizes.

Worked with Back-end Developers to ensure that the front-end and back-end components worked together correctly.

Lead Front-end Developer

TRIBETEQ 2021 - 2022

Contributed to building responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.

Collaborated with web designers and back-end developers to create user-friendly web applications.

Led and monitored a team of front-end developers.

Optimized web pages for maximum speed and compatibility across different browsers and devices.

EDUCATION

• BSc. Computer Science

BABCOCK UNIVERSITY

2016 - 2020

SKILLS

HTML CSS Javascript React Wordpress Bootstrap Data Structures Git	HTML	CSS	Javascript	React	Wordpress	Bootstrap	Data Structures	Git
---	------	-----	------------	-------	-----------	-----------	-----------------	-----